<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Community_docs on E-Heza Documentation</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/community_docs/</link><description>Recent content in Community_docs on E-Heza Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/community_docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contributing to E-Heza</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/community_docs/contribute-eheza/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/community_docs/contribute-eheza/</guid><description>Contributing Code E-Heza is an open source project and welcomes contributions from the developer community. The E-Heza project uses PHP, Javascript, Drupal CMS, Elm frontend language, among other frameworks and languages. If you are able to make a code contribution, There are other ways to contribute below.
If you are interested in making a code contribution and would like to learn more about the technologies that we use, see the developer documentation in the project repository.</description></item><item><title>E-Heza Governance</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/community_docs/eheza-governance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/community_docs/eheza-governance/</guid><description>The purpose of this document is to provide descriptions of the various internal and external committees that contribute to the governance of E-Heza. These committees of stakeholders contribute to the successful expansion of E-Heza in terms of clinical functionality, software development and geography.
This document summarizes committee members' roles and responsibilities, as well as the committee member selection criteria:
The following committees are affiliated with E-Heza:
E-Heza Executive Committee TIP Global Health Steering Committee Ministry of Health Digital Health Technical Working Group (TWG) Reproductive and Maternal Newborn child health Technical Working Group Community Health Technical Working Group E-Heza Partners Technical Working Group E-Heza Executive Committee The primary function of the E-Heza executive committee is to contribute to the efficient operation of E-Heza.</description></item><item><title>E-Heza Project Road Map</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/community_docs/eheza-roadmap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/community_docs/eheza-roadmap/</guid><description>The E-Heza Road Map is maintained by the E-Heza Executive Committee. Features requests can be made through the documented feature request process.
Feature Description Release Date Release Status Notes Group Nutrition Assessment (Health Center) Provides nutrition screening for groups of mother/child pairs participating in PMTCT groups. June 2018 0.1.0 complete - Nutrition Activitiy includes measurements for height, weight, MUAC, photo of child, family planning</description></item><item><title>Funding Support for E-Heza</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/community_docs/eheza-funding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/community_docs/eheza-funding/</guid><description> Funder Name 2017 2018 2019 2020 2021 2022 2023 Izumi Foundation X X X X X X X Grand Challenges Canada X X Imago Dei Fund X X X X X Segal Family Foundation X X X X X X Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson Foundation X X X X X CRI Foundation X X X X Elsa Miller Foundation X X Conservation, Food, &amp;amp; Health Foundation X X</description></item></channel></rss>