<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Developer_docs on E-Heza Documentation</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/developer_docs/</link><description>Recent content in Developer_docs on E-Heza Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/developer_docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>E-Heza Data Dictionary</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/developer_docs/data-dictionary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/developer_docs/data-dictionary/</guid><description>E-Heza has over 1000 fields of data (and growing) - the data dictionary can be found here.</description></item><item><title>E-Heza Technical Specs</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/developer_docs/technical-specs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/developer_docs/technical-specs/</guid><description>Language/Framework On the front end, E-Heza is developed in Elm, an open source and functional, statically-typed language that compiles to JavaScript. On the back end, the application is served by Drupal, an open source PHP content management system. The front and back ends communicate through a Restful API developed as a contributed module to Drupal.
Database Application data is stored in a database and accessed through Drupal’s database abstraction layer.</description></item><item><title>Quickstart Guide for Development</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/developer_docs/quickstart-guide-for-development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/developer_docs/quickstart-guide-for-development/</guid><description>Introduction TIP’s E-Heza Data Solutions is a digital app designed by and for the frontline health worker that can be used on a smartphone or tablet. E-Heza captures essential data at the point of care to improve the health of mother and child by providing frontline health workers with immediate insights to help personalize information and advice, and help the mother track the well-being of her child.
Technical stack Elm for the mobile frontend Drupal for the backend Try out on GitPod The project is integrated with GitPod.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade to Offline Sync App Version</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/developer_docs/upgrade-offline-sync/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/developer_docs/upgrade-offline-sync/</guid><description>Download the App and Prepare Your Environment Download the app The first step is to download the new app from site. This is achieved simply by opening the app pinned to your homepage or pointing the chrome browser to the app page at &amp;lt;base domain&amp;gt;/app.
The newest version should download automatically - indicated by the status icon at the top right corner of the screen. Yellow means a download is in progress, green means the download is complete.</description></item></channel></rss>