<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Policy_docs on E-Heza Documentation</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/</link><description>Recent content in Policy_docs on E-Heza Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Agreement Template</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/business-agreement-template/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/business-agreement-template/</guid><description>TIP Global Health Master Services Agreement This Master Services Agreement (this “Agreement”), effective as of [●] (the “Effective Date”), is entered into by and between TIP Global Health, a California 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization with offices located at 7492 Soquel Drive, Suite D, Aptos, California 95003 (“Licensor”) and [LICENSEE NAME], a [STATE OF ORGANIZATION] [ENTITY TYPE] with offices located at [ADDRESS] (“Licensee”). Licensor and Licensee may be referred to herein collectively as the “Parties” or individually as a “Party.</description></item><item><title>Data Protection Policy</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/data-protection-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/data-protection-policy/</guid><description>Definitions
Organization means TIP Global Health, a company registered as a non for profit corporation in the USA (California) and Rwanda DPA means the Data Protection Act 2018 which implements the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation and is used as a guideline rather than a legislative authority in determining data policies. Responsible Person means the E-Heza Project Director. Register of Systems means a register of all systems or contexts in which personal data is processed by the Organization.</description></item><item><title>Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion Policy</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/dei-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/dei-policy/</guid><description>TIP Global Health is committed to fostering, cultivating and preserving a culture of diversity, equity and inclusion. Our human capital is our most valuable asset. The collective sum of the individual differences, life experiences, knowledge, inventiveness, innovation, self-expression, unique capabilities and talent that our employees invest in their work represents a significant part of not only our culture, but our reputation and company’s achievements.
We embrace and encourage our employees’ differences in age, color, disability, ethnicity, family or marital status, gender identity or expression, language, national origin, physical and mental ability, political affiliation, race, religion, sexual orientation, socio-economic status, veteran status, and other characteristics that make our employees unique.</description></item><item><title>Do No Harm Policy</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/do-no-harm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/do-no-harm/</guid><description>TIP Global Health envisions a world in which high quality healthcare leads to inclusive, empowered, and healthy communities. To achieve our goals, it is critical that TIP mitigates the risk of harm while maximizing benefits to all stakeholders. TIP Global Health and all associated organizational entities, including E-Heza Data Solutions, holds itself accountable to the highest standards of protection for our staff, partners, patients, and community members at large. TIP operates under strong ‘do no harm’ principles in all aspects of our work.</description></item><item><title>Gender Analysis &amp; Strategy</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/gender-equality-strategy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/gender-equality-strategy/</guid><description>Introduction Gender inequity is pervasive across many aspects of life, including educational attainment, financial independence, employment, and security or social protections. Healthcare is not exempt from the impact of such inequalities. Through an in-depth analysis of gender inequities facing both healthcare recipients and healthcare providers, we aim to determine what critical gender-related issues, challenges, and opportunities are most relevant to TIP Global Health’s innovation, E-Heza Data Solutions. We also seek to lay out clear priorities and an actionable implementation plan to achieve improvements toward gender equality.</description></item><item><title>Harassment Prevention Policy</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/harrassment-prevention-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/harrassment-prevention-policy/</guid><description>TIP Global Health is committed to providing a work environment free of any form of harassment. Our policy prohibits sexual harassment and harassment because of or perception of pregnancy, childbirth or related medical conditions, race, religious creed, color, gender, national origin, citizenship, ancestry, physical or mental disability, medical condition, marital status, sexual orientation, age, gender, gender identity, genetic information, gender expression, veteran status, or any other basis protected by federal, state or local law or ordinance or regulation.</description></item><item><title>Non-Discrimination Clause</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/non-discrimination-clause/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/non-discrimination-clause/</guid><description>ARTICLE 13 NON-DISCRIMINATION CLAUSE No officer, director, employee, or agent of TIP Global Health shall discriminate on the basis of or perception of race, color, religion (creed), citizenship, gender identity, genetic information, gender, gender expression, age, national origin (ancestry), disability, marital status, sexual orientation, or military status, in any of its activities or operations. These activities include, but are not limited to, hiring and firing of staff, selection of volunteers and vendors, and provision of services.</description></item><item><title>Protected Health Information Confidentiality Agreement</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/confidentiality-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/policy_docs/confidentiality-policy/</guid><description>Workforce-Staff and Contractors I understand that I require information to perform my duties at TIP Global Health by which I am engaged or for which I am performing services. This information may include, but is not limited to, information on patients, employees, other workforce members, donors, research, and financial and business operations. Confidential information may be in any form, e.g., written, electronic, oral, overheard or observed. I also understand that access to all confidential information is granted on a need-to-know basis.</description></item></channel></rss>