<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>E-Heza Documentation</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/</link><description>Recent content on E-Heza Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title> Acute Illness Module</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/acute-illness-module-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/acute-illness-module-chw/</guid><description>Acute Illness Module @ Community Level The Acute Illness module for CHW’s is used as the first line of care. CHW’s are able to diagnose patients on the spot, provide immediate care and health education, or direct patients to a health center to receive further care.
There are four main activities in the Acute Illness module: Symptom Review, Exposure/Travel History, Prior Treatment History, and Physical Exam.
Symptom Review allows a CHW to do an inventory of General, Respiratory, and Gastrointestinal symptoms to inform their diagnosis.</description></item><item><title>Acute Illness Module</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/acute-illness-module/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/acute-illness-module/</guid><description>Acute Illness @ Health Centers The Acute Illness module at Health Center’s is able to collect more information than at the CHW level as there are more tools at the Nurse’s disposal at the Health Center.
There are four main activities in the Acute Illness module: Symptom Review, Exposure/Travel History, Prior Treatment History, and Physical Exam.
Symptom Review allows a Nurse to do an inventory of General, Respiratory, and Gastrointestinal symptoms to inform their diagnosis.</description></item><item><title>Antenatal Care Module</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/antenatal-care-module/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/antenatal-care-module/</guid><description>Antenatal Care @ Health Centers The Antenatal Care (ANC) module at the Health Center works collaboratively with the CHW module. A nurse at a Health Center can see what has happened in CHW visits and seamlessly continue care.
There are nine main activities in the ANC module. Activities appear in the main tray of E-Heza depending on which of their ANC visits a patient is on. The activities are Pregnancy Dating, History, Examination, Family Planning, Medication, Malaria Prevention, Medication Distribution, Danger Signs, Labs, and Photo.</description></item><item><title>Antenatal Care Module</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/antenatal-care-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/antenatal-care-chw/</guid><description>Antenatal Care Module @ Community Level The Antenatal Care (ANC) module for CHW’s works collaboratively with the CHW module. A nurse at a Health Center can see what has happened in CHW visits and seamlessly continue care.
There are 7 main activities in this module and they appear when appropriate in the pregnancy. The main activities are: Pregnancy Dating, Labs, Danger Signs, Birth Plan, Health Education, Appointment Confirmation, and Pregnancy Outcome.</description></item><item><title>Case Management + Progress Reports</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/case-management-progress-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/case-management-progress-reports/</guid><description>Case Management allows both CHW’s and nurses to manage their patients. On the CHW side, Case Management includes patients who have an active acute illness, an active pregnancy, are participating in a child nutrition program, and general family planning patients. At the Health Center, nurses are able to manage ANC patients awaiting lab results and perform COVID contact tracing calls.
E-Heza supports a variety of patient progress reports including U5 Pediatric Progress Reports, Antenatal Progress Reports, general Acute Illness Reports, and Demographic Reports.</description></item><item><title>Contributing to E-Heza</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/contribute-eheza/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/contribute-eheza/</guid><description>Contributing Code E-Heza is an open source project and welcomes contributions from the developer community. The E-Heza project uses PHP, Javascript, Drupal CMS, Elm frontend language, among other frameworks and languages. If you are able to make a code contribution, There are other ways to contribute below.
If you are interested in making a code contribution and would like to learn more about the technologies that we use, see the developer documentation in the project repository.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/covid-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/covid-19/</guid><description>COVID-19 @ Health Centers Acute Illness encounters at both the Health Center and CHW level accommodate for a COVID-19 diagnosis. At the Health Center level, this specific flow allows for rapid testing, medication distribution, and contact tracing.
When a patient is suspected of having COVID at the Health Center level, they will be given a rapid test to confirm a diagnosis. They will then undergo a more in-depth physical exam to determine how severe their COVID case is.</description></item><item><title>Create Group</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/create-group/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/create-group/</guid><description>On the E-Heza Admin Menu click Create Group or go directly to path /node/add/clinic.
In the Title field enter the group name.
In the Health Center field add the name of the Health Center that this group is under.
Leave the UUID field blank.
Note: A Group should never be deleted when there are other entities (mothers/children/nurses) referring to it.</description></item><item><title>Create Group Encounter</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/create-group-encounter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/create-group-encounter/</guid><description>&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Note:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; This workflow will be deprecated when nurses will be able to create sessions on demand using the app. In order to schedule a group encounter, create a new Group Encounter, assign the relevant Group, and specify the Scheduled Date for the measurements. This needs to be done in advance, using the Drupal admin UI. It will then show up in the client app as being available for data entry, until the Close On date.</description></item><item><title>Create/Edit Nurse</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/create-nurse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/create-nurse/</guid><description>Creating a new nurse On the E-Heza Admin Menu click Create Nurse or go directly to path /node/add/nurse.
Complete these fields:
Title - The name of the nurse - you can use any alpha-numeric characters PIN Code - leave this field blank for a new nurse - a PIN will be auto-generated Groups - select a group(s) that the Nurse is allowed to participate in. E-mail Address - a valid email address of the user Roles - check the relevant box: Nurse or Administrator (an administrator can perform certain admin actions on a device - this does not allow the person to login to the back end).</description></item><item><title>Creating/Pairing a Device</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/pairing-device/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/pairing-device/</guid><description>Pairing a New Device You will need an admin (not nurse) password to the backend to perform this step. All admin users and passwords were kept from the previous app version. To pair a device with the backend, you need to create the &amp;ldquo;Device&amp;rdquo; on the backend at https://eheza.global.
On the E-Heza Admin Menu click Create Device or go directly to path /node/add/device.
Fill in the name with something that identifies the device (e.</description></item><item><title>Delete a person, relationship, group</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/delete-a-person-relationship-group/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/delete-a-person-relationship-group/</guid><description>How to mark a person/relationship or group as deleted Go to https://eheza.global/admin/content and search for the name of the person or group you wish to mark as deleted.
Marking a person/relationship/group as deleted is done by editing the person/relationship/group, checking the deleted checkbox, and saving:
Note the following: A Person cannot be marked as deleted if it has measurements. Marking a person as deleted causes all its relationships and participants (group and encounter) to be marked as deleted.</description></item><item><title>E-Heza Project Roadmap</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/eheza-roadmap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/eheza-roadmap/</guid><description>layout: default title: E-Heza Project Roadmap section: &amp;ldquo;Community&amp;rdquo; Feature Description Release Date Release Status Notes Group Nutrition Assessment (Health Center) Provides nutrition screening for groups of mother/child pairs participating in PMTCT groups. June 2018 0.1.0 complete - Nutrition Activitiy includes measurements for height, weight, MUAC, photo of child, family planning
- On the fly Z-score calculation
- PWA provides offline access - data is synced via user initiated command.</description></item><item><title>Environments and Databases</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/environments-databases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/environments-databases/</guid><description>Why We Have Multiple Environments/Databases Gives us a place to see and test ongoing work independent of the live environment or other environments that shouldn’t be disturbed. Some environments need constant “repairing/re-syncing” due to ongoing development It allows us to separate private data from anonymous data Databases We will be working with three types of databases:
Production: This is the database in the live environment with private patient data.</description></item><item><title>Funding Support for E-Heza</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/eheza-funding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/eheza-funding/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Group vs. Individual Encounters</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/group-vs.individual-encounters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/group-vs.individual-encounters/</guid><description>Group vs Individual Encounter E-Heza supports both group and individual encounters at both the CHW and Health Center levels. This feature allows health care workers to perform large group assessments more efficiently and reduces burnout.
At the CHW level, E-Heza is built out to accommodate both 1:1 visits, as well as group encounters. A CHW can choose to start a group encounter which allows them to collect height, weight, MUAC, Nutrition, Family Planning, and Photos for each individual in a group setting.</description></item><item><title>Importing patient data in bulk (backend)</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/importing-patient-data-in-bulk-backend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/importing-patient-data-in-bulk-backend/</guid><description>Format of spreadsheet The template can be found here.
Use this folder to copy the templates and add google sheets to be referenced for the bulk import.
Child TEMPLATE to copy
(red is required, blue is optional)
Mother/Caregiver TEMPLATE to copy
(red is required, blue is optional)
Notes Date format: dd-Jan-yyyy (2 digits for day: 01-Jan-1990) Last name: All upper case National ID: 16 digits (if not known, leave cell blank) The names for the health center and group need to match exactly those in the backend A Mother needs to be added only once, even if she has multiple children Mapping As a first instance, we use National ID to map children to mothers.</description></item><item><title>Login to the Admin Site</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/admin-login/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/admin-login/</guid><description> Go to https://eheza.global Enter your username and password Click Log in button To change your password:
Click on My account. Click Edit. Enter new password in both fields: Password and Confirm password. Click Save.</description></item><item><title>Login to the App</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/login-device/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/login-device/</guid><description>Nurses login to a device using a PIN code that is assigned by an admin or is automatically generated when the nurse is created. A nurse cannot reset their own PIN code or request that it be reset in any automated way.
Notes about login and logout.
Login is not dependent on being connected to the Internet. You can login and logout while offline. The device should be secured in another way using device security as the device will contain data related to the current Health Centers.</description></item><item><title>Nutrition Module</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/chw-nutrition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/chw-nutrition/</guid><description>Nutrition Module @ Community Level The Nutrition Module at the CHW level allows early detection of malnutrition in children at the community level, allowing them to be referred to a health center nutrition program.
General Nutrition Encounter
There are five activities in the Nutrition Module at the CHW level: MUAC, nutrition, height, weight, and photo.
MUAC collects the circumference of the child’s arm in centimeters and indicates immediately with a red or green arrow if the child is above or below where they should be.</description></item><item><title>Nutrition Module</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/nutrition-module/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/nutrition-module/</guid><description>Nutrition Module @ Health Centers The Nutrition Module allows nurses at Health Centers to screen children for signs of malnutrition, refer them to the correct program, and then follow up via group nutrition encounters.
There are 5 activities in the Nutrition Module: height, MUAC, weight, nutrition, and photo.
Height collects the height of a child in centimeters, automatically calculates their Z-Score, and highlights with a red or green arrow if they are above or below where they should be.</description></item><item><title>Registering Patients (on the App)</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/registering-patients-front/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/registering-patients-front/</guid><description>To begin registering a patient (or a related set of patients), tap &amp;ldquo;Register a Participant&amp;rdquo; on the main screen of the app.
&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Note:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; The above screen will be deprecated for a new entry flow. Next, you may search to see if the person you are registering already exists or you can directly register a person you know is new.
Searching for an existing patient Enter the beginning letters of a first or second name (only the beginning letters will match, the system will not match the middle of a name).</description></item><item><title>Resetting the Environment</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/reset-environment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/reset-environment/</guid><description>Resetting the environment is done in extreme circumstances and should only be done with the guidance of an administrator. All data will be lost on the device and you will need to perform a lengthy initial sync. On an Android device (the directions are slightly different for a desktop, see below):
In the chrome browser, go to https://eheza.global/app (do this in the Chrome browser even if you have the app pinned to your homepage on the device).</description></item><item><title>Standard Pediatric Visit Module</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/standard-pediatric-visit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/standard-pediatric-visit/</guid><description>Standard Pediatric Visit The Standard Pediatric Visit module (SPV) at the Health Center focuses on the health and development of children under 5 years of age. Complete with early childhood development (ECD), nutrition, and immunization tracking, SPV helps ensure that young children are on track in all aspects of development.
There are 6 main activities in the SPV module: Danger Signs, Nutrition Assessment, Immunizations, ECD, medication, and photo.
Danger Signs is comprised of two sub-activities: symptom review and vitals.</description></item><item><title>The Admin Menu</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/admin-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/admin-menu/</guid><description>The E-Heza Admin Menu provides access to be able to create content on the backend. These tasks should only be accessed by an administrator that is familiar with the content structure.
The following options (test) are available:
[Create Device]({{ site.url &amp;gt;}}/pairing-device): This is used to setup and pair a new device. [Create Nurse]({{ site.url &amp;gt;}}/create-nurse): To add a new nurse to be able to access the application. Create Person: To add a new patient to the system - this task can now be accomplished in the [front-end application]({{ site.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting the initial sync</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/troubleshooting-sync/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/troubleshooting-sync/</guid><description>The initial sync on the device can take a very long time (up to 30 minutes with a good internet connection) and it can pause during the process if it encounters problems. This sync only needs to be performed once for a device, but it is important that it is done fully before the device can be used. You can access the device status page using the icon at the top middle of the screen.</description></item><item><title>Update the App</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/update-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/update-app/</guid><description>Updating the app is achieved simply by opening the app pinned to your homepage or pointing the chrome browser to the app page: https://eheza.global/app
The newest version should download automatically - indicated by the status icon at the top right corner of the screen. Yellow means a download is in progress, green means the download is complete. You should visit the deployment status page by tapping on the status indicator.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade to Offline Sync App Version</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/upgrade-offline-sync/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/docs/upgrade-offline-sync/</guid><description>Download the App and Prepare Your Environment Download the app The first step is to download the new app from site. This is achieved simply by opening the app pinned to your homepage or pointing the chrome browser to the app page: https://eheza.global/app
The newest version should download automatically - indicated by the status icon at the top right corner of the screen. Yellow means a download is in progress, green means the download is complete.</description></item></channel></rss>