<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Research_docs on E-Heza Documentation</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/research_docs/</link><description>Recent content in Research_docs on E-Heza Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/research_docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction: Functional Specifications</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/research_docs/fsd-intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/research_docs/fsd-intro/</guid><description>Scope &amp;amp; Purpose E-Heza Data Solutions is a comprehensive point-of-care digital health platform that ensures high quality, efficient care when and where it is needed most. First established to serve the Rwandan primary care ecosystem that is comprised of nurses and midwives in health centers and community health workers (CHW) in villages, E-Heza is designed to support existing government health systems and facilitates the most common workflows of frontline health workers at the community and facility levels in Sub Saharan Africa (SSA) where large electronic medical record (EMR) systems are often impractical and where existing CHW tools struggle to adequately support the two-way communication and data management capacity that facilitates an effective and efficient local healthcare ecosystem at scale.</description></item><item><title>Personas &amp; Workflows</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/research_docs/personas-workflows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/research_docs/personas-workflows/</guid><description>Personas Nurse A nurse works in a health center and is charged with direct patient care as well as administrative work and record keeping. The nurse sees patients in large group encounters as well as in individual encounters for nutrition screening, antenatal care, and acute illness.
Goals
To record crucial patient information efficiently and accurately To improve the health outcomes of their patients. Needs
Relief from extra administrative work that removes focus from patient care.</description></item><item><title>Posts &amp; White Papers</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/research_docs/posts-papers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/research_docs/posts-papers/</guid><description>Posts https://tipglobalhealth.org/first-impressions-of-tip-global-healths-transformative-stage/ https://tipglobalhealth.org/e-heza-data-solutions-selected-for-healthtech-hub-africa/ https://tipglobalhealth.org/tips-strategic-growth-made-possible-by-cri-foundation-support/ https://tipglobalhealth.org/smartphones-an-essential-tool-to-empower-community-health-workers/ https://tipglobalhealth.org/isas-day/ https://tipglobalhealth.org/aheza-community-health-initiative-at-work-improving-the-nutrition-status-of-children/ https://tipglobalhealth.org/empowering-community-health-workers-through-digital-tools/
Other Papers https://www.devex.com/news/health-tech-solutions-for-low-resource-areas-emerge-from-mit-solve-94891 https://dqo52087pnd5x.cloudfront.net/posters/docs/gatesopenres-195756.pdf https://asia.stanford.edu/event/public-health-delivery-systems-building-trust-through-hope/</description></item><item><title>Technical Architecture</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/research_docs/technical-architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/research_docs/technical-architecture/</guid><description>E-Heza is built with a decoupled architecture providing both a “frontend” (where healthcare workers enter data) and a “backend” that receives and organizes that data. The frontend is developed in Elm, an open source and functional, statically-typed language that compiles to JavaScript. The back end application is served by Drupal, an open source PHP content management system. The front and back ends communicate through a RESTful API, which is modeled on digital health standards including FHIR-HL7.</description></item><item><title>WHO Classification of Digital Health Interventions</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/research_docs/who-classifications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/research_docs/who-classifications/</guid><description>The World Health Organization (WHO) Classification of Digital Health Interventions v1.0 attempts to create a shared language to describe the uses of digital technology for health. According to the WHO, the classification of digital health interventions (DHIs) categorizes the different ways in which digital and mobile technologies are being used to support health system needs.
E-Heza is classified primarily as a Electronic Medical Record (Category H), but also serves interventions in the following categories:</description></item></channel></rss>