<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>User_docs on E-Heza Documentation</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/</link><description>Recent content in User_docs on E-Heza Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Acute Illness Assessment - Health Center Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/ai-hc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/ai-hc/</guid><description>The Acute Illness module at Health Center’s is able to collect more information than at the CHW level as there are more tools at the Nurse’s disposal at the Health Center.
There are four main activities in the Acute Illness module: Symptom Review, Exposure/Travel History, Prior Treatment History, and Physical Exam.
Symptom Review allows a Nurse to do an inventory of General, Respiratory, and Gastrointestinal symptoms to inform their diagnosis.</description></item><item><title>Diagnosis, Treatment, and Referral of Childhood Illnesses - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/acute-illness-module-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/acute-illness-module-chw/</guid><description>Established to support CHWs' ability to continue their work despite COVID-19. Allows CHWs to screen for COVID-19, identify, isolate and refer suspects. If COVID-19 not suspected, allows CHWs to evaluate for, diagnose, treat, and refer if needed cases of malaria, diarrhea, and pneumonia. Decision matrices tailored to the needs of all age groups and subpopulations (ex. pregnant women). This workflow supports traditional U5 ICCM as well as all age groups</description></item><item><title>Group Encounters - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/group-nutrition-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/group-nutrition-chw/</guid><description>CHWs conduct monthly group nutrition assessments. This module allows CHWs to take attendance, and to toggle between individual mother/child pairs and activities. Z scores are automatically calculated. Family planning assessments are conducted at the same time, and a mother&amp;rsquo;s record is linked to her child for easy joint evaluations.
Mother/Child Pair View
Activity View
Weight Activity featuring Z-Score Weight for Age
Height Activity featuring Z-Score Height for Age</description></item><item><title>Group vs. Individual Encounters</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/group-vs.individual-encounters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/group-vs.individual-encounters/</guid><description>Group vs Individual Encounter E-Heza supports both group and individual encounters at both the CHW and Health Center levels. This feature allows health care workers to perform large group assessments more efficiently and reduces burnout.
At the CHW level, E-Heza is built out to accommodate both 1:1 visits, as well as group encounters. A CHW can choose to start a group encounter which allows them to collect height, weight, MUAC, Nutrition, Family Planning, and Photos for each individual in a group setting.</description></item><item><title>Pregnancy - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/antenatal-care-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/antenatal-care-chw/</guid><description>This module allows CHWs to identify and register pregnant women in their villages. CHWs can provide health education tailored to the pregnant woman&amp;rsquo;s trimester of pregnancy and she can review pregnancy progress on the progress report. The tool prompts the CHW to schedule her follow up home visit and allows her to tell the pregnant woman when she needs to attend her next facility ANC visit.
The Antenatal Care (ANC) module for CHW’s works collaboratively with the CHW module.</description></item><item><title>Pregnancy - Health Center Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/antenatal-care-module/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/antenatal-care-module/</guid><description>This module allows midwives and nurses to provide full-scope antenatal care services. The module is trimester-responsive while ensuring tasks expected in earlier trimesters are completed if a pregnant woman accesses care later in her pregnancy. It features automated calculations for the estimated due date, gestational age, and Gravida/Para.
The Antenatal Care (ANC) module at the Health Center works collaboratively with the CHW module. A nurse at a Health Center can see what has happened in CHW visits and seamlessly continue care.</description></item><item><title>Standard Pediatric Care Visit</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/standard-pediatric-visit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/standard-pediatric-visit/</guid><description>The Standard Pediatric Visit module (SPV) at the Health Center focuses on the health and development of children under 5 years of age. Complete with early childhood development (ECD), nutrition, and immunization tracking, SPV helps ensure that young children are on track in all aspects of development.
There are 6 main activities in the SPV module: Danger Signs, Nutrition Assessment, Immunizations, ECD, medication, and photo.
Danger Signs is comprised of two sub-activities: symptom review and vitals.</description></item><item><title>ANC Progress Report - Health Center Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/anc-progress-report-hc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/anc-progress-report-hc/</guid><description>A single progress report organizes all important information required for effective antenatal care. This includes risk factors, obstetrical and medical history, milestones tracker, and trends for BMI and fundal height to inform care decisions and engage pregnant women in the progress of their pregnancies. CHW activities also appear on this shared progress report.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19 Diagnosis, Treatment and Referral - Health Center Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/covid-diagnosis-hc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/covid-diagnosis-hc/</guid><description>Acute Illness encounters at both the Health Center and CHW level accommodate for a COVID-19 diagnosis. At the Health Center level, this specific flow allows for rapid testing, medication distribution, and contact tracing.
When a patient is suspected of having COVID at the Health Center level, they will be given a rapid test to confirm a diagnosis. They will then undergo a more in-depth physical exam to determine how severe their COVID case is.</description></item><item><title>Decision Support and Next Step Guidance</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/decision-support-and-next-step-guidance-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/decision-support-and-next-step-guidance-1/</guid><description>Decision Support and Next Step Guidance
Using the inputs from the above sections, E-Heza is then able to direct CHWs on suspected diagnosis and next steps.</description></item><item><title>Decision Support and Next Step Guidance Antenatal Care</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/decision-support-and-next-step-guidance-antenatal-care/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/decision-support-and-next-step-guidance-antenatal-care/</guid><description>Decision Support and Next Step Guidance
Using the inputs from the above sections, E-Heza is then able to direct CHWs on suspected diagnosis and next steps.</description></item><item><title>Individual Encounters - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/individual-nutrition-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/individual-nutrition-chw/</guid><description>Originally developed to allow CHWs to conduct one-to-one nutrition encounters for children at home when the pandemic struck and group encounters were not allowed. Continues to be used for children who have missed the group nutrition assessment. Features all the same activities as a group encounter.</description></item><item><title>Individual Nutrition Assessment</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/individual-nutrition-hc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/individual-nutrition-hc/</guid><description>The Nutrition Module allows nurses at Health Centers to screen children for signs of malnutrition, refer them to the correct program, and then follow up via group nutrition encounters.
There are 5 activities in the Nutrition Module: height, MUAC, weight, nutrition, and photo.
Height collects the height of a child in centimeters, automatically calculates their Z-Score, and highlights with a red or green arrow if they are above or below where they should be.</description></item><item><title>ANC Progress Report - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/anc-progress-report-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/anc-progress-report-chw/</guid><description>A single progress report organizes all important information required for effective Antenatal Care. This includes all evaluations and documentation conducted at health centers - such as risk factors, obstetrical and medical history, milestones tracker, and trends for BMI and fundal height to inform care decisions and engage pregnant women in the progress of their pregnancies. CHWs review this progress report with pregnant women during their home visits. The progress report also documents the CHW visits and types of health education provided.</description></item><item><title>Diagnosis, Treatment, and Referral of Malnutrition - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/chw-nutrition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/chw-nutrition/</guid><description>The Nutrition Module at the CHW level allows early detection of malnutrition in children at the community level, allowing them to be referred to a health center nutrition program.
There are five activities in the Nutrition Module at the CHW level: MUAC, nutrition, height, weight, and photo.
MUAC collects the circumference of the child’s arm in centimeters and indicates immediately with a red or green arrow if the child is above or below where they should be.</description></item><item><title>Group Nutrition Assessment</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/group-nutrition-hc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/group-nutrition-hc/</guid><description>This module allows nurses at Health Centers to take run group encounters for supplemental nutrition programs. They are able to take attendance and to toggle between individual mother/child pairs and activities. Z scores are automatically calculated. Family planning assessments are conducted at the same time, and a mother&amp;rsquo;s record is linked to her child for easy joint evaluations.
Mother/Child Pair View
Activity View
Weight Activity featuring Z-Score Weight for Age</description></item><item><title>IMCI Progress Reports - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/ai-progress-reports-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/ai-progress-reports-chw/</guid><description>This provides a summary of the patient&amp;rsquo;s symptoms, vital signs if taken, diagnosis, treatment, and next steps.
E-Heza supports a variety of patient progress reports including U5 Pediatric, Antenatal, Childhood Illnesses, and Demographic Progress Reports. These reports allow health care workers to track the progress of their patients over time as individuals and as a group.</description></item><item><title>Laboratory with Pending Results Management</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/laboratory-with-pending-results-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/laboratory-with-pending-results-management/</guid><description>This activity is embedded into the antenatal care module. The midwife or nurse can conduct point of care tests and document the results into E-Heza. She can also order lab tests to be performed at the lab on the day of care. When results are available, a Laboratory case management system notifies her that results are ready to be reviewed with the pregnant woman.
An in-depth look at the ANC labs module can be found below:</description></item><item><title>Acute Illness Diagnosis, Treatment, Management, and Referral - Health Center Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/ai-diagnosis-hc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/ai-diagnosis-hc/</guid><description>The Acute Illness module at Health Center’s is able to collect more information than at the CHW level as there are more tools at the Nurse’s disposal at the Health Center.
There are four main activities in the Acute Illness module: Symptom Review, Exposure/Travel History, Prior Treatment History, and Physical Exam.
Symptom Review allows a Nurse to do an inventory of General, Respiratory, and Gastrointestinal symptoms to inform their diagnosis.</description></item><item><title>Decision Support and Next Step Guidance</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/decision-support-and-next-step-guidance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/decision-support-and-next-step-guidance/</guid><description>Decision Support and Next Step Guidance Using the inputs from the above sections, E-Heza is then able to direct CHWs on suspected diagnosis and next steps.</description></item><item><title>IMCI Case Management - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/ai-case-managment-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/ai-case-managment-chw/</guid><description>Provides case management support for all cases of acute illness (COVID-19, Malaria, Pneumonia, Diarrhea) in the community. Reminds CHWs to conduct follow-up assessments to determine if the case is improving or declining. Allows CHWs to schedule follow-ups for people they have referred to facilities due to complications.</description></item><item><title>Integrated Management of Childhood Illnesses (IMCI) - Health Center Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/acute-illness-module/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/acute-illness-module/</guid><description>The Acute Illness module at Health Center’s is able to collect more information than at the CHW level as there are more tools at the Nurse’s disposal at the Health Center.
There are four main activities in the Acute Illness module: Symptom Review, Exposure/Travel History, Prior Treatment History, and Physical Exam.
Symptom Review allows a Nurse to do an inventory of General, Respiratory, and Gastrointestinal symptoms to inform their diagnosis.</description></item><item><title>Post-Partum - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/anc-postpartum-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/anc-postpartum-chw/</guid><description>CHWs are expected to conduct home visits for all post-partum women within 2 days of delivery. This visit allows CHWs to document pregnancy outcomes, assess for danger signs, refer to health centers if indicated, provide health education and anticipatory guidance, and register newborns.
Document Pregnancy Outcomes
Assessing Danger Signs
Newborn Enrollment</description></item><item><title>Post-Partum - Health Center Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/anc-postpartum-hc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/anc-postpartum-hc/</guid><description>Allows nurses to document pregnancy outcome.</description></item><item><title>Acute Illness Progress Reports</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/ai-progress-reports-hc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/ai-progress-reports-hc/</guid><description>This provides a summary of the patient&amp;rsquo;s symptoms, vital signs if taken, diagnosis, treatment, and next steps.
E-Heza supports a variety of patient progress reports including U5 Pediatric, Antenatal, Childhood Illnesses, and Demographic Progress Reports. These reports allow health care workers to track the progress of their patients over time as individuals and as a group.</description></item><item><title>Community Acute Illness Dashboards</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/ai-dashboards-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/ai-dashboards-chw/</guid><description>Provides aggregated data to support data reporting and to identify early trends in fevers and other infectious diseases.
You can see both dashboards and case management in action below:</description></item><item><title>Comprehensive Pediatric Progress Report</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/pediatric-progress-report-hc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/pediatric-progress-report-hc/</guid><description>A single progress report organizes all important information required for effective pediatric care. This includes all evaluations and documentation conducted at health centers - such as acute illness history, immunizations, early child education milestones, growth and weight charts, malnutrition indicator tracking, and follow-up appointment schedule. This progress report can be seen by both the CHW and the health centers and tracks information at both levels.</description></item><item><title>Newborn - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/chw-newborn-exam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/chw-newborn-exam/</guid><description>Allows CHWs to conduct a health assessment of the newborn and document vaccines that were given after birth. CHWs are reminded to provide health education and anticipatory guidance. Supports assessment, diagnosis, treatment and referral of malnutrition. Allows CHWs to schedule a follow up visit on their case management module if needed. A progress report outlines problems identified, immunizaiton record summary and growth trends.
The Newborn Exam is performed, when applicable, after an Antenatal Post-Partum encounter, once a newborn has been registered in E-Heza.</description></item><item><title>Nutrition Case Management - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/nutrition-case-management-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/nutrition-case-management-chw/</guid><description>Allows CHWs to track children with malnutrition. CHWs can initiate a home visit from this screen.</description></item><item><title>ANC Case Management - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/anc-case-management-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/anc-case-management-chw/</guid><description>Allows CHWs to see all pregnant women in their villages and to track when they are due for a home visit. CHWs can conduct a follow-up ANC visit or post-partum visit from this module.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19 Contact Tracing Case Management - Health Center Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/covid-contact-documentation-hc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/covid-contact-documentation-hc/</guid><description>Contact tracing allows the nurse to collect contact information and store it in the E-Heza system for follow-up. Contacts then appear in the nurse’s case management and are followed up with via telephone for ten days past contact with the index patient. If a patient has symptoms of COVID, they are directed to their nearest health center. This feature is currently used only for COVID-19 and can easily be used for other instances that require it.</description></item><item><title>Home Visits - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/nutrition-home-visits-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/nutrition-home-visits-chw/</guid><description>At the CHW level, E-Heza also supports Nutrition Home Visits. This allows CHWs to conduct the MoH-recommended home health assessment for malnourished children. This includes an assessment of feeding practices, caregiving, hygiene, and food security.
Feeding allows a CHW to follow up on if the child is receiving the correct amounts of food supplement, type of supplemental food, and any problems the child may be facing to eat adequate amounts of the food.</description></item><item><title>ANC Dashboards - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/anc-dashboards-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/anc-dashboards-chw/</guid><description>Summarizes aggregated data required for data reporting. Includes the number of newly identified pregnancies, currently pregnant women, pregnant women within 4 months of their due dates, women with danger signs, home deliveries and health facility deliveries.
You can see a more in-depth look at dashboards below:</description></item><item><title>Nutrition Dashboards - CHW Workflow</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/nutrition-dashboards-chw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/nutrition-dashboards-chw/</guid><description>Allows CHWs to see the number of nutrition encounters she has conducted, the percentage of children with good nutrition, and the prevalence/incidence of malnutrition by subtype.</description></item><item><title>COVID-19 Contact Tracing (within Acute Illness Module)</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/covid-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/covid-19/</guid><description>After being diagnosed with COVID-19, the patient is then asked to recount the names of everyone they can remember coming into contact with since their COVID-19 symptoms began. The nurse will collect the contact’s name, phone number, and as much geographic data that’s known in E-Heza. This data is later pushed to Case Management for contact tracing purposes.</description></item><item><title>Login to the App</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/login-device/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/login-device/</guid><description>Nurses login to a device using a PIN code that is assigned by an admin or is automatically generated when the nurse is created. A nurse cannot reset their own PIN code or request that it be reset in any automated way.
Notes about login and logout.
Login is not dependent on being connected to the Internet. You can login and logout while offline. The device should be secured in another way using device security as the device will contain data related to the current Health Centers.</description></item><item><title>Nutrition Module</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/nutrition-module/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/nutrition-module/</guid><description>Nutrition Module @ Health Centers The Nutrition Module allows nurses at Health Centers to screen children for signs of malnutrition, refer them to the correct program, and then follow up via group nutrition encounters.
There are 5 activities in the Nutrition Module: height, MUAC, weight, nutrition, and photo.
Height collects the height of a child in centimeters, automatically calculates their Z-Score, and highlights with a red or green arrow if they are above or below where they should be.</description></item><item><title>Registering Patients (on the App)</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/registering-patients-front/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/registering-patients-front/</guid><description>To begin registering a patient (or a related set of patients), tap &amp;ldquo;Register a Participant&amp;rdquo; on the main screen of the app.
&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Note:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; The above screen will be deprecated for a new entry flow. Next, you may search to see if the person you are registering already exists or you can directly register a person you know is new.
Searching for an existing patient Enter the beginning letters of a first or second name (only the beginning letters will match, the system will not match the middle of a name).</description></item><item><title>Resetting the Environment</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/reset-environment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/reset-environment/</guid><description>Resetting the environment is done in extreme circumstances and should only be done with the guidance of an administrator. All data will be lost on the device and you will need to perform a lengthy initial sync. On an Android device (the directions are slightly different for a desktop, see below):
In the chrome browser, go to the app page at &amp;lt;base domain&amp;gt;/app (do this in the Chrome browser even if you have the app pinned to your homepage on the device).</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting the initial sync</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/troubleshooting-sync/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/troubleshooting-sync/</guid><description>The initial sync on the device can take a very long time (up to 30 minutes with a good internet connection) and it can pause during the process if it encounters problems. This sync only needs to be performed once for a device, but it is important that it is done fully before the device can be used. You can access the device status page using the icon at the top middle of the screen.</description></item><item><title>Update the App</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/update-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/update-app/</guid><description>Updating the app is achieved simply by opening the app pinned to your homepage or pointing the chrome browser the app page at &amp;lt;base domain&amp;gt;/app.
The newest version should download automatically - indicated by the status icon at the top right corner of the screen. Yellow means a download is in progress, green means the download is complete. You should visit the deployment status page by tapping on the status indicator.</description></item><item><title>Video Demonstration of E-Heza CHW Modules</title><link>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/isas-day-video-training/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tip-global-health.github.io/eheza-documentation/user_docs/isas-day-video-training/</guid><description>This video playlist document&amp;rsquo;s Isa&amp;rsquo;s Day - a day in the life of a CHW showing various aspects of E-Heza&amp;rsquo;s CHW modules.</description></item></channel></rss>